好的  如果你们喝咖啡了  你们需要每个月罚款5美元
Okay, so you'll need to put in five dollars a month if you drink coffee.
还有什么  我看看
Uh, let's see--
大家都知道的  领养日就在本周六了
Oh, as you know, Adoption Day's Saturday.
伯顿·法林也非常善良地捐出了他的律师
And, uh... Burton Fallin has been kind enough to donate his attorneys
和他的办公室  才让我们有机会做这件事
and his offices so we can make the whole thing happen.
但是你们要记住  你们会跟一些不熟悉收养流程的
But, you need to remember that you'll be working with lawyers
律师一起干活
that aren't familiar with the adoption process.
所以你们要监督他们的工作  但是一定不要得罪了他们
So oversee their work, definitely, but don't offend anyone.
知道了吗
Okay?
呃  会议结束
Uh, that's it.
你们的案件分配在会议室
Your case assignments are in the meeting room.
明天见
See ya tomorrow.
尼克  尼克
Nick. Nick.
你的缓刑官刚才来电话了
Your probation officer just called.
什么事
Why?
黑泽尔公园的操场那边发生一件事故
There was an incident over at the Hazel Park playground.
一个三岁的小孩踩到了废弃针头得了肝炎
A three-year-old kid stepped on a discarded needle and got hepatitis.
这跟我有什么关系
What has that got to do with me?
政府想要把公园清理一下  可能要举行媒体拍照会
Well, the City wants to clean up the park now, like a photo-op kinda thing,
他们想让社区服务缓刑犯做这事
and they want to use community service probationers to do it.
- 所以我要去清理公园了  - 是的
- l'm gonna be on a clean-up crew? - Yeah.
这个是计在你社区服务时间内的  而且这件事也是为了孩子
lt credits against your hours and, you know, it's for the kids.
老兄  有零钱吗
Hey, man. Spare some change?
好的  缓刑犯们  我叫查克  都给我听好了
Okay, probationers. My name is Chuck. Listen the hell up.
各位  今天我们是有规矩的
There's rules here today, gentlemen.
法林先生
Mr. Fallin.
不许打电话  不许用传呼机
No cell phones and no pagers.
- 嗨  - 我抓到你打电话了
- Hey. - l catch you talking on a cell phone.
嗨
Hey.
我是朗尼  朗尼·格兰迪  还记得吗
Lonnie. Lonnie Grandy?
你来这里干嘛
Yeah, what're you doin' here?
你知道的
Just, you know,
来帮帮忙
helping out.
我还以为来这里的都是  呃
Uh, l thought this was just for, uh--
- 是的  - 你知道的
- Right. - You know?
好的  都过来这边的野餐椅子上领下你们的橡胶手套
All right, just pick up your rubber gloves over here at the picnic benches.
把吸毒工具
Discard all drug paraphernalia,
避孕套  还有啤酒罐都扔到医用垃圾袋里
condoms and beer bottles into the medical waste bags.
我一直很担心你  老兄
l was worried about you, man.
- 我还以为你死了呢  - 没有
- l thought you, like, died or something. - No.
我以为你有事发生了  但是
Yeah, l thought like something had happened but,
我是说  我想
uh, l mean, l guess--
你不记得我了  对不对
You don't remember me, do you?
不好意思
l'm sorry.
几年前  你是我的律师
You represented me a couple years ago.
我偷了我养父母的信用卡
l stole credit cards
from my foster parents.
他们把我赶出去了
They kicked me out.
哦  对对
Right. Right.
几个月前  我试着打过你电话好几次
You know, l tried calling you a couple times, like, a few months ago.
- 你收到我的信息了吗  - 没有  没有收到
- Did you get my messages or-- - No. Nope. No messages.
那么
Huh, well--
我打过好多次电话
Yeah, l tried calling you a bunch of times.
我们现在从外向内开始干活
All right, we'll start working from the outside of the park, in.
记住   明天
And remember tomorrow
我们要开始涂漆  记得穿个旧的鞋子过来
we start painting, so wear old shoes.
嘘  没事的  弗吉尼亚
Shh. It's okay, Virginia.
- 你有钱吗  - 就在这儿
- You got money? - Yeah, right here.
你好
Hello.
这是您的孩子吗
ls-- is this your kid?
法外真情
第三季  第七集
翻译   马丁  倪
校对  油 球
特效  转轮 枪
- 嗨  - 嘿
- Hi. - Hey.
打扫那边怎么样
How was the clean-up crew?
挺好的
Oh, it was fine, l guess.
你这里不需要帮忙  对不对
Uh, you don't need any help around here, do you?
不如帮我给小孩换个尿片吧
Uh, well, how about changing a diaper?
我回办公室了
l'll be in my office.
好的
Okay.
不要动  跟我来
No, no, no. Come with me.
伊莱亚娜  拉斐尔  那我们周日见了  好吗
lleana. Raphael. See you on Saturday then. Okay?
谢谢你  法林先生
Thank you so much, Mr. Fallin.
祝你好运
Good luck.
下一个  哈尔和利雅·莱温斯基
Okay, uh, Hal and Ria Lewinski.
- 我叫刘易克  - 抱歉
- Lewicki. - Oh, l'm sorry.
- 我是伯顿·法林  - 你好  我是哈尔  这是利雅
- Burton Fallin. - Hi, l'm Hal. This is Ria.
这是特伦斯
And this is Terence.
你好  你好吗  嗨
Hi. How are you? Hey.
- 我们进去吧  - 谢谢
- Go right on in. - Thanks.
- 真是太幸运了  - 是啊
- This is such a blessing. - Yeah.
我们好不容易才走到了今天
We've been through so much to make it to this day.
当然
l'm sure.
在这之前  我们
Before this we, uh--
之前
lt was, uh--
这是在我们遇到特伦斯前生母亲罗兹之前
Well, we were, uh-- well, this was before we met Roz, Terence's birth mother.
我们被骗了
We were scammed.
我们之前想要通过互联网领养小孩
We tried to adopt over the internet.
他们告送我小孩子在分娩的时候就死了
They told us the baby had died during childbirth.
- 哦  - 利雅当时都崩溃了
- Oh. - Ria was-- Ria was devastated.
哈尔带着我又尝试再去领养  我不愿意  但
Hal talked me into trying to adopt again. l didn't want to but--
嗯  好吧
Hum, well--
她来了  罗兹
Oh, there she is. Roz!
罗兹  这里
Roz! In here.
罗兹在皮特酒店打扫卫生
Roz is a cleaning lady at the Ft. Pitt Hotel.
嗨
Oh. Hi.
不好意思  这些人
Sorry, these guys, uh--
没事  进来吧  进来
That's all right. Come on in. Come on in.
罗兹  这是伯顿·法林  由他来处理特伦斯的收养案子
Roz, this is Burton Fallin. He's handling Terence's adoption.
- 你还好吗  - 你好
- How are ya? - Hey.
很高兴见到你  坐吧
Good to see you. Sit down there.
我需要你把刘易克的最后一张表填好
Filling out this last form for the Lewickis here.
- 你要抱抱特伦斯吗  - 不  不要
- Do you want to hold Terence? - No, no, no.
我想  我最好不要
l think-- l think l'd better not do that.
我会忍不住哭  所以
'Cause l'll just bawl so...
罗兹还有两个孩子  他们现在已经是青少年了
Roz has two other children. They're teenagers.
罗兹要给他们吃穿很不容易
And she's had a hard time supporting them.
她的长子在很多寄养家庭待过了
And, well, the older one's been in a few foster homes.
特伦斯的出生是个意外
And Terence here was unexpected.
这就是为什么我要做这个的原因
That's why l'm doing this.
因为我养不起他
'Cause l can't afford to keep Terence.
我知道这个决定  对你来说很难
Oh, l'm sure it was a very difficult decision for you to make.
是的
lt was.
而签下这个文件就好像
And, signing those papers was, like...
能不能现在让我抱抱他
Can l hold him now, please?
给
Here.
好
Okay.
我要回去上班了  我跟我的经理说我
l'm gonna go back to work 'cause l told my manager that l--
我去一趟洗手间  谢谢你  祝你好运  上帝保佑
l was gonna go to the bathroom so thank you. Good luck. God bless.
你要去哪儿
Where ya going?
我找不到我的钱包了
Well, l can't find my wallet.
我想我可能落在公园了
l think l might've dropped it in the park.
- 哦  - 你需要钱吗还是
- Oh. - Do you need money or anything?
不不  也可能在我的车上
No. No. You know, it's probably in my car.
好吧
Okay.
电梯在哪儿
Where's the elevator?
- 你还好吗  - 我没事
- Are you okay - l'm fine.
我只是  电梯在哪儿
l'm just-- Where's the elevator?
那儿  需要我帮什么忙吗
lt's over there. Could l help you with something?
不  我没事  我刚才只是找不到电梯
No, l'm fine. l just wanted to know where the elevator was?
- 啊  - 天呐
- Aah! - Oh, my God.
哦  不
Oh... no.
快叫救护车
Call-- call an ambulance.
嘿  你找到你的钱包了吗
Hey, did you find your wallet?
没有
No.
你记不记得一个叫朗尼·格兰迪的孩子
You remember a kid named Lonnie Grandy?
- 谁  - 朗尼·格兰迪
- Who? - Lonnie Grandy.
他说一年多以前我们有
He says we represented him
接过他的一个案子
about eighteen months ago.
不记得  怎么了
No. Why?
没什么
Uh, no reason.
好吧  额
Okay. Well, um...
今晚我买饭回去  我们七点家里见
l'm gonna bring dinner home tonight. l'll see you at seven.
好的
All right.
你现在和露露住在一起  还是
You and Lulu living together now, or...
是啊
Yeah.
哦
Oh.
她有没有告诉你那个意外事故
She tell ya about the accident?
什么意外事故
What accident?
有个女人在大堂
Well, this woman fell over
被一个装满文件的箱子绊倒了
a box of files in the lobby
胳膊有几个地方摔断了  而且
and broke her armin a couple places and--
有人看到了吗
Any witnesses?
很多人看到了
About a dozen.
好吧
Well, great.
如果她想起诉我们的话
So if she wants to sue us
肯定有很多证人能证明这是我们的疏忽
she won't have any problem proving negligence.
是啊
Yeah.
我已经给在东北的艾伦·伯克威茨打过电话了
l already called Alan Berkowitz over at Northeastern.
好的  很好
All right. Good.
好吧
Yeah, okay.
那么  关于露露  我  呃
Well, hey, um-- 'bout Lulu, l'm, uh--
我真的为你们感到高兴
l'm happy as hell for ya.
谢谢
Thank you.
我在想要不要给你们送个礼物
l was thinking about getting you guys a gift or something.
你需要什么吗  或者
ls there anything you-- you need or...
- 礼物吗  - 是
- A gift?= - Yeah.
不用
No.
谢谢  但是我们不用
Uh, thank you, uh, but we're fine.
好吧  我只是很开心
Well, l'm-- l'm just very pleased
所有的事现在的发展
about the way everything's turning out
都挺好的
and all the way around.
我很开心
l'm just very pleased.
嗯
Right.
给
There ya go.
真的好激动  这些孩子明天就会
Well, it's gonna be exciting all these kids being--
在一天之内都会被收养
having their adoptions finalized on one day.
在法院吗
ln court?
是啊
Yeah.
他们现在已经跟新的家庭生活在一起了
And they're already living with their families,
但是还需要法官来宣布它的合法性  所以
but it takes a judge to make it legal so...
就像是结婚一样
Kinda like getting married.
是啊
Yeah.
甚至比结婚还要好
Maybe even better.
香农
Shannon.
什么事
Yeah?
你觉得  呃
How would you feel about, uh--
我是说  如果我收养你的话  你有什么意见
l mean, what would you think about my, uh, adopting you?
请问  你有火吗
You got a light? Excuse me.
你好  你有没有火
Hey, you got a light?
- 没有  你从哪里来
- No. - Where you from?
- 莎迪赛德  - 莎迪赛德
- Shadyside. - Shadyside?
来自莎迪赛德的打工的可不多
Not a lot of laborers from Shadyside.
我不是打工的
Well, l'm not a laborer.
独自学习的人  莎迪赛德
The doer alone learneth, Shadyside.
你说什么
What's that?
要不要约  二十块钱
You want a date? Twenty bucks.
你叫什么名字  孩子
What's your name, son?
什么
What's that?
- 你的名字  - 尼克·法林
- Your name. - Nick Fallin.
加快速度  法林  我们不能光刷漆就刷一个月
Get your back into it, Franklin. We can't spend a month out here.
查克上个月监督我高速公路清理的工作
Chuck supervised me last month-- highway clean-up.
他对新来的就会指手画脚
He just picks on the new guys.
你注销了我的卡
Cancelled my cards.
你在说什么
What're you talking about?
我的钱包
My wallet.
你知道吗  当你帮我打官司的时候  我真的很尊敬你
You know, when you represented me l really looked up to you, man.
帮了我之后  我以为你所做的
After you helped me out, l thought what you did--
我以为你人真很好
thought you were, like, the greatest guy.
所以你就偷走了我的钱包吗
So you did steal my wallet.
你还是不明白
You don't get it.
你一但成年了
Uh, once you're eighteen--
你就消失了
you just disappear.
有一天  很多人帮助我
l mean, one day l had all this help.
社会劳动者表现得有多在乎我一样
Social workers acting like that you gave a crap about me
接着第二天
and then the next day--
我就得自己靠自己了
Well, the next day, l was on my own, you know?
我当时非常迷茫
Yeah, l was totally lost.
这时我遇到一个人  他说如果我把我的助学贷款给他投资
So then this guy, you see, he tells me if l invest my school loan money with him
他可以在一周或者一个月之内双倍给我
he can, like, double it in a week or a month or something, yeah?
所以我就把钱给他了
So l give it to him.
- 真聪明  - 这个人跟我说
- That was smart. - This guy, he said
他说他把钱都输在了生物技术的股票上了  但是
he, uh-- he said he lost it all on some biotech stock, but--
所以我就给你打电话  但是你从没给我回过电话
So then l called you to see if you might help and you never called me back.
朗尼  能不能把钱包还我
Lonnie, l just want me wallet back.
而且大学  他们没有收到我的学费
And the college, right? See, they're weren't paid.
我也拿不出钱去缴学费  对吧
And l can't come up with the money, right?
所以我就经常在卡内基·梅隆附近闲逛
So-- So sometimes l hang around Carnegie Mellon.
我抢了一个富家子弟的信用卡
l ripped off this rich kid's credit card
- 然后我就被抓了  - 你有没有在听我说话
- and l got caught. - You not hearing me?
- 把我的钱包还我   - 所以我就没念得了大学
- l want my wallet back. - See l'm not in college!
我现在在缓刑期
l'm on probation.
全都是因为你当时的冷漠 没有给我回电话
All because you never bothered to call me back.
肱骨上部碎了
The upper humerus was shattered.
半径移位骨折  复发性尺骨骨折
Displaced fracture of the radius. Compound fracture of the ulna.
需要做很多次手术  而且康复期很长
lt's gonna take several surgeries and a long rehabilitation period.
好吧
All right.
我们做了一些计算
We've run some numbers.
医疗费  事业损失  精神损失费
Medical costs, lost wages, pain and sumering.
50万美元吗
Five hundred thousand dollars?
是法林先生的律师所  法林先生的错
Mr. Fallin's premises. Mr. Fallin's hazard.
应当由法林先生承担责任
Mr. Fallin's liability.
我们不答应50万美元
We'll never go to five hundred thousand.
肯普夫女士的手腕可能再也不能像以前一样灵活了
Ms. Kempf may not regain full use of her wrist.
陪审团可能会给她七位数
A jury might give her seven figures.
Fifty.
最少
Light.
罗恩  你已经研究这个案子一整天了
Ron, you've been working on this case one day.
我是说  这次会议我可以给你20000美元
l mean, you're walking away with $20,000 for one meeting.
好吧  公平点  30万吧
All right, the fair number is three hundred.
你们想要谈到公平的价格  要花很多功夫
lt's gonna take a lot of work on your part to get to the fair number.
- 15万  - 13.7万
- One fifty. - One thirty seven.
成交
Done.
我晚点打电话给你
l'll call you later today.
好的  罗恩  谢谢
Okay, Ron. Thanks.
- 没事  - 很高兴见到你
- Sure. - Good to see you.
- 很高兴见到你  - 伯顿  你的保险费扣除额为5万美元
- Nice seeing you, too. - Your deductible is $50,000 Burton.
我会让我们的代表联系你  制定新的保险费
l'll have our rep contact you with your new premium.
好的  谢谢  老艾  谢谢
Yeah, thanks, Al. Thanks.
你知道吗  露露对发生的这些感到抱歉
You know, uh, Lulu, she feels-- she feels terrible about this.
哦  告诉她不用担心
Oh, no. Tell her not to worry about that.
但是  儿子  我还有件事想跟你聊一聊
But, uh, l did want to talk to you about something, Nicholas.
我
l'm, uh--
我很认真的在想收养香农的事情
l've been seriously considering adopting Shannon.
哦
Oh.
我昨晚问了她的意见
Asked her consent last night and,
她说她愿意  所以
she said, 'yes', so...
好  需要我帮忙吗
Right. Well, you need my help with anything?
不用  谢谢
No. But, thanks.
试试上  露露帮了我很多忙
Matter of fact, Lulu's helping me out.
露露啊  太好了  她知道自己在做什么
Lulu. Great. Well, she knows what she's doing.
- 很好  - 好吧
- Good. - All right.
好的  保重  另外
Okay, take care. Oh, by the way,
你有没有问她关于乔迁礼物的事
did you ask her about that housewarming gift?
没有  我忘了
No. Forgot.
那你问问她
Well, ask her.
劳拉·唐纳龙是哪位
Laura Donnellon?
什么  哦  是我
What? Oh, that's me.
唐纳龙小姐  今天下午会有一个收容所听证会
So Miss Donnellon, there will be a shelter hearing later this afternoon.
嗯
Right.
鉴于你的情况
And, uh, given your situation
法官不可能把孩子的监护权给你
there's no way that the judge will grant you custody of your child.
知道了
Got it.
你
Do you, uh,
你有没有这个地区的家人愿意收养佛吉尼亚的
have any family in the region that might be willing to take Virginia?
有  我家人
Yeah. My family.
我有个儿子
l've got a son.
我的父母收留了他
My parents took him
他们不让我见他  如果你是在问我的父母的话
and won't let me see him, if that's what you're talking about.
你父母知道你女儿的事情吗
Do your parents know about your daughter?
我想他们也快知道了
Guess they're about to find out, huh?
好吧  他们住在匹兹堡吗
Yeah, well, uh, do they live in Pittsburgh?
是  在福克斯教堂
Yeah, in Fox Chapel.
我爸在机场旁边开了一家建筑公司
My dad has that construction company by the airport.
唐纳纶建筑公司是你爸开的啊
Donnellon Construction?
是的  是我爸的
My dad, that's his company.
好吧
Huh. Okay.
现在对你来说
Uh, well, the best thing for you to do
今天下午一定要去听证会
is to go to the hearing this afternoon
跟法官和陪审团说你要去上父母育儿课  要去找工作
and, just be open to taking parenting classes and finding a job
并且要明确自己的药物治疗计划
and definitely a drug treatment program.
我之前也说过
Been there.
劳拉  你来这里告诉我你想要得到帮助
Laura, you're coming here tells me that you want help.
少私寡欲
Ever desiring, one sees the manifestation.
知足者富
Ever desireless, one sees the mystery.
什么
What?
道
The Tao.
意思是  利欲会蒙蔽你的双眼
lt means wanting things makes you blind.
所以你不想要帮助
So then you don't want help?
我本身没有问题
l am not a problem to be fixed.
好吧
Okay, um--
那我们就跟法官说  你愿意
Well, we'll just tell the judge that you're, willing to start
开始一些新的改变  我们先这样开始吧
making some changes and we'll go from there.
劳拉
Laura?
什么
What?
没事
Nothing.
我联系了社区大学
l called the community college.
他们同意你建立一个新的还款计划  你可以重新报名了
They've agreed to set up a new payment plan for you so you can re-enroll.
哦  我的天
Oh, man.
你拯救了我
You just, like, totally fixed my life.
我只是打了一个电话而已
l just made a call.
你  我简直不敢相信
You-- l can't even believe it.
我不知道说什么好了
l don't-- l don't know what to say.
打这个电话  报上我的名字
Call this number. Use my name
他们会帮你
and they'll work it out with you.
我就跟他们说  我的律师尼克·法林让我打电话给你们说你们会帮我吗
l just tell them my attorney, Nick Fallin, told me to call and then they'll help?
是的
Yeah.
我拿走的钱
l'll pay you back.
我会还给你的
The cash l took.
- 好吧  - 所以
- Right. - Yeah, so--
你想进来喝一杯吗
You want to come in or something for a beer?
喂  尼克
Hey, Nick?
弗吉尼亚·唐纳龙被发现一人独自待在一辆旧车的前排座位上
Virginia Donnellon was found unattended in the front seat of an old car.
她的妈妈  劳拉·唐纳龙  是一个吸毒者
Her mother, Laura Donnellon, is believed to be a drug addict.
在她回到匹兹堡的近半年里  她已经由于
She has been arrested twice for prostitution since her return
卖淫被捕两次了
to Pittsburgh in the last six months.
你的建议呢
Your recommendation?
这个  弗吉尼亚不能就住车里啊
Well, Virginia cannot be returned to a car.
她的外祖父母  理查德和玛丽·唐纳论
Her maternal grandparents, Richard and Mary Donnellon,
已经同意会给这个孩子一个家
have agreed to provide a home for the child.
他们准备要养育这个婴儿吗
They're prepared to raise an infant?
理查德和玛丽已经收养了劳拉的第一个孩子
Richard and Mary are already raising Laura's first child,
一个叫托马斯的十四岁男孩
a fourteen-year-old boy named Thomas.
但是  他们只有一个条件
But, they do, however, have one condition.
什么条件
A condition?
他们要求
They request that, uh--
他们的女儿在没有戒毒完全之前
their daughter, Laura, not have access to Virginia until she completes
没有探看弗吉尼亚的权利
a drug rehabilitation program.
阿奇女士  你的当事人来了吗
Ms. Archer, is your client coming?
法官大人  我想她正在来的路上
Uh, l think that she's on her way, Your Honor.
你认为
You think?
在没有见到这位妈妈之前我不准备
l'm not prepared to enter a ruling
宣判结果
until l meet the mother.
明天早上十一点再次开庭
We'll reconvene tomorrow morning at eleven o'clock.
你的听证会你怎么没去
You missed your hearing.
我爸在那儿
My dad was there.
- 是的  他在  - 不
- Yeah, he was and-- - No.
我的意思是我爸在那儿
l mean, my dad was there.
你在说什么
l don't understand.
我跟我爸没有话说
l don't talk to my dad.
你的父母已经暂时照顾弗吉尼亚了
Your parents have taken temporary custody of Virginia.
你觉得这是毒品的原因吗
You think this is about drugs?
这个  劳拉
Well, Laura--
你知道吗  我以班级第二名的
You know, l graduated
成绩从福克斯教堂高中毕业
second in my class at Fox Chapel High School.
我在布朗大学念了三个学期
l went to Brown for three semesters.
然后呢
Okay.
我的爸爸  迪克  开着他的奔驰
My dad, Dick, drives up to Providence
去了普罗维登斯
in his Mercedes.
我当时怀着托马斯
l was pregnant with Thomas.
他走进我的宿舍让我收拾行李
He walks into my dorm room and he tells me to pack.
跟我说要带我回家
He tells me that we're going home.
回来的路上  迪克一句话也没说
All the way back, Dick doesn't say a word
直到他把车停在了梅西赫斯特戒毒所
until we pull up in front of Mercyhurst Rehab Clinic
然后他终于开口说话了
then Dick finally talks.
他说  滚出来
He says, ''Get out.''
你想让我怎么做  劳拉
What do you want me to do, Laura?
你有你的选择
'You are free, therefore choose#
我会跟法官说关于你的孩子
l'm gonna tell the court that you are amenable to your baby
跟着外公外婆住没有意见
being placed with your parents.
嗯
Yeah.
我也会请求法庭提供本县应该给你
And l'll tell the court to support
提供的康复服务给你
your rehabilitation and to give you all of the services the County
这样你就能回家了
has to offer so that you can go back home.
你的听证会在明天早上十一点开始
Your hearing is tomorrow at eleven.
明天早上  在那儿见
Tomorrow morning. l'll see ya there.
罗伊  非常感谢你可以来
Well, l appreciate you coming by, Roy.
没事
Sure.
给
Here ya go.
在佛罗里达怎么样
So how was-- how was Florida?
就是那个介绍你去的小姐  她怎么样了
You know that lady l introduced you to,
- 谢丽尔·安吗  - 是的
- Cheryl Ann? - Yeah.
她拿走了我的钱把我甩了
Took my money and dumped me.
- 是吗  - 是啊
- Really? - Uh-huh.
很抱歉听到这个消息
Well, l'm sorry to hear that.
我相信  你肯定不会有这样的烦恼
Yeah, well, l'm sure you don't have those kind of problems.
你这么成功
Not with your success.
我不知道
l don't know about that.
但是  罗伊啊  我想跟你聊聊
But, Roy, l-- l just wanted to talk to you
关于香农的将来
a little bit about Shannon's future.
好啊
Okay.
你可以想象下  最好的高中  最好的大学
Well, you can imagine, you know, the best high schools, college,
研究生学位和一份稳定的工作
and graduate degree. A solid job.
你是在说  我给不了这些
And you're saying l can't provide those things.
我觉得你给不了  罗伊
l'm not so sure you can, Roy.
听着  香农可以成为任何她
See Shannon could be
想成为的人
whatever she wants to be.
有着你和我那个年代没有的
Have the opportunities to make choices that, uh--
选择的机会
well, you and l never had when we were growing up.
然后呢
Yeah?
这就是我想说的
That's what this is all about.
给香农更多的选择
Having options for Shannon, but--
所以之前有个律师小姐给我打电话
So that lawyer lady that called
说了一些关于要不要选择
said something about, should l choose to do this,
放弃香农的抚养权的事
that l'd be terminating my parental responsibilities.
你会的
You would be.
- 我能不能考虑一下  -当然
- l have time to think about it? - Absolutely.
如果你签字了
Oh, and if you do sign,
你还有四十天的反悔时间
there will be a forty day revocation period, so...
好吧
Okay.
- 好吗  - 好的
- Okay? - Uh-huh.
伯顿  我回来了
Burton, l'm home.
嗨  亲爱的
Hey, honey.
嗨
Hey.
嗨  罗伊
Hey, Roy.
嗨  亲爱的
Hey, sweetheart.
嗨
Hey.
给你买的
This is for you.
谢谢
Thanks.
我给社区大学财务室的
So l called that guy at the community college,
那个人打电话了  他愿意给我重新制定一个还款计划
bursar's office, and he's willing to set up a payment schedule with me.
如果我付了前三期的款  他们会重新给我发放他们的贷款
And, if l keep up my first three payments, they'll re-issue my loan.
- 不错啊  - 是的
- There ya go. - Yeah.
问题是  我现在没有工作
See the thing is, though l don't have a job.
我是说  谢谢你
l mean, thanks and that, but, you know,
但是我现在没有办法偿还任何钱
l can't really amord to pay anything right now.
然后呢
Okay.
你能帮我找一份工作吗
Uh, can you help me get a job?
我不知道
Well, l don't know.
老兄  你们律师所里肯定有人可以帮我找到一份工作吧
Oh, come on. You must know somebody at the clinic who can help me get a job.
富兰克林  我希望你给每个人
Franklin, l hope you brought
都买了一杯咖啡
enough coffee for everyone.
我可以问你个问题吗
Ask you something?
你说
Sure.
我交了个女朋友  她叫辛迪
l got this girlfriend. Her name's Cindy.
她来自福克斯教堂
She's from Fox Chapel.
她在卡耐基·梅隆大学学戏剧专业
She's a-- she's a drama major at Carnegie Mellon.
她想成为一名电影明星
She wants to be a movie star.
我也跟她说了我也在卡耐基·梅隆大学念书
So l've been telling Cindy that, you know, that l go to CMU.
我学的是计算机
That l'm working with computers.
哦
Oh.
如果我告诉她我是个孤儿
You know, if l told her l was an orphan
或者告诉她我甚至没有上过社区大学
or who doesn't even go to community college--
我还因为偷盗信用卡被处缓刑
You know, who's on probation for stealing credit cards, and--
女生肯定都不想听到这些
That's not exactly what a girl like that wants to hear.
- 肯定不想  - 是啊
- No. - Right.
也许  如果你帮我找到了一份工作
So maybe, like, if you can help me get a job
我能重新去学校念书  也许她就会觉得和我在一起以后会有希望
and that and l re-enroll in school then she'll think l'm a guy with a future.
是  也许她会
Yeah, she might.
那么
Well?
谢谢你帮我
Thanks for helping me.
罗兹  你怎么样了
How are you, Roz?
很疼
l'm-- It hurts a lot.
抱歉
l'm so sorry.
听着  我
Listen, l--
我只想
l just--
把特伦斯要回来
l want Terence back now.
什么
What?
我不想要她的唯一的原因就是我养不起她
The only reason l gave him up was because l couldn't amord another kid.
所以  我们能不能就当这些都没有发生过
So if we could just tear everything up.
但是你都签了字了
But, you signed the papers.
文件上写着我可以改变主意
The form said l could change my mind.
但是当初给你时间考虑了
But, you had a time period
时间已经过了  对不对  法林先生
that's run out. Right, Mr. Fallin?
这不在我的专业范围内
Well, this is not my area of expertise
但是确实  你的撤销的时间已经过去了  但是
but, yeah, your revocation period has come and gone, but--
但是收养的程序还没有通过
But the adoption hasn't gone through yet.
不  不行  他是我们的了
No. This is-- No. He's ours now.
我们已经走完程序了
We've been through the process.
明天只是走个流程而已
Tomorrow is just supposed to be a formality.
拜托你  把特伦斯还给我
Please, give Terence back to me.
还给我
Give him back.
求你了
Please.
法官大人  我的当事人要求每周有两个小时的探望时间
Your Honor, my client requests two hours of supervised visitation per week
每个月可以有一个星期天可以去看孩子
as well as one Sunday a month.
如果劳拉想要探望孩子  在安排探望之前
lf any visitations are scheduled my clients would like them
我的当事人必须知道劳拉的
to be contingent upon Laura's successful
戒毒康复情况是成功的
completion of a drug rehabilitation program.
好的法官大人  劳拉·唐纳龙原因
Well, Your Honor, Laura Donnellon is willing to enter
进入戒毒所接受治疗
a drug treatment program,
但是她要求立刻有接触孩子的权利
but she would like immediate access to her child.
重申  我方当事人只有在劳拉康复之前
Again, my clients are only willing to take
不允许接触孩子
the child if their daughter is not allowed
才能答应会收留孩子
access until after her rehabilitation.
否则  尽管他们会很难过
OtheM/ise, as much as this pains them,
但是他们也不会收留孩子
they will not take the child.
法官大人  我能说话吗
Your Honor, may l speak?
请说
Go ahead.
尼采说  家庭的爱
Um, Nietzsche wrote that family love
是令人苦恼及不断重复的混乱模式
is messy of an annoying and repetitive pattern.
就像是坏掉地墙纸
Like bad wallpaper.
我感觉  对我父母来说
And l've been kinda like that to my parents.
我不断重复这些  非常让人讨厌
l mean, repetitive in my actions and probably more than annoying.
我的意思是
What l mean to say is
我也想回家
that l would like to go home, too.
如果
lf, um--
如果我现在说还来得及的话
if this is an appropriate time to say so.
我们来这里是讨论收留你的女儿的问题的
We are here only to discuss the placement of your daughter.
对  抱歉
Right. l'm sorry.
如果劳拉·唐纳龙想要去探望佛吉尼亚的话
lf Laura Donnellon wishes to visit Virginia,
她必须提前一天通知
she must give twenty-four hours' notice
而且她是清醒的
and she must be sober.
我的当事人接受
My clients accept the terms.
这是板上钉钉的事情  对不对
This is a done deal, right?
我的意思是  他们不能把特伦斯带走
l mean, they can't make us give Terence back.
我不确定  但是
l'm not sure, but, uh--
她已经不要特伦斯了
She already walked away from Terence.
也签了那些文件
She signed the forms.
可撤销期也已经过了
She waited through the revocation period.
事情已经结束了
lt's done.
好了  那我们继续弄收养的程序把
Fine, let's just move on with the adoption proceedings.
我觉得你说得对
l think you're right.
罗兹确实说过因为她养不起这个孩子她才放弃她得
Roz did say that she only gave up the baby because she couldn't amord him.
是啊
Right.
她现在有照顾特伦斯的钱了
And now she has the money to take care of him.
是
Right.
所以如果她不想给我们的话  我不知道
So l don't know if l can take this baby from her,
我能不能从她身边抢走这个孩子
if she doesn't want to give him to us.
利雅
Ria.
我做不到
l can't do it.
我不能要这个孩子
l can't take this baby
如果她不想给我们的话
if she doesn't want to give him to us.
在我们做决定之前
Look, let's just meet with the judge
我们先去法庭听听法官怎么说  好吗
first before you decide anything. Okay?
我太蠢了  我看起来就像个傻逼一样
l was so stupid. l made a fool of myself.
没有  你没有  你刚才很棒
No, you didn't. You were great.
我跟你的父母谈过了
l, uh-- l talked to your parents.
我们安排了明天早上开个会
We scheduled a meeting tomorrow morning.
十点钟  在我的办公室
Ten o'clock. My office.
- 明天早上吗  - 对
- Tomorrow morning. - Right.
如果你能来的话  如果你下定决心了
Now, if you can make the meeting, l mean, if you can be straight.
嗯
Right.
那么  我们将会一起讨论让你回家这件事
Then, they'll discuss the possibility of you going home.
好的
Okay.
这是个好消息  是个非常不错的开始
So this is great news. It's a great start.
他们看起来愿意吗
They seemed into it?
是的  看起来原因的
Yeah, they did. They did.
所以
Uh, so--
如果你明天赶过来不方便的话
you know, if you're gonna have trouble getting to the meeting, uh--
斯坦威克斯有一个收容所  你今晚可待在哪儿
there's a shelter on Stanwix. You can stay there tonight.
不  我不去
No. l'd rather not.
明天早上十点
Tomorrow morning. Ten o'clock.
这次我会去的
l'll be there this time.
你最好可以
You better.
刘易克先生  刘易克太太  你们是说
Mr. and Mrs. Lewicki, are you saying
你们明天放弃收养了吗
you will not finalize the adoption tomorrow?
是的  法官大人
Yes, Your Honor.
好的
Okay.
孩子会暂时归法院管辖
The child will remain under the jurisdiction of this court.
肯普夫太太  周一会举行
Mrs. Kempf, there will be a shelter hearing on Monday,
你收养你的亲生孩子的听证会
regarding your becoming a foster parent to your own child.
谢谢
Thank you.
你们大家明白吗
You understand, all of you,
这是一个非常特殊的案子
this is a highly unusual situation.
但是刘易克夫妇答应会归还孩子
But, the Lewickis said they'll give him back.
我现在也有些钱
And l have some money now.
所以
So...
香农
Shannon.
嗨
Hi.
我觉得我们应该谈谈
l thought maybe we should talk.
为什么
Why?
你爸爸想要收养我
Your dad wants to adopt me.
我听说了
Uh, l heard.
我也想这样  我爸爸也答应了
And, l want him to and my dad agreed,
所以  就这么决定了
so it's gonna happen.
好吧
Okay.
我很兴奋
And l'm real excited.
然后我想到了你
But then l started thinking about you.
我怎么了
'Bout me?
我在想  你会不会有点
And l started to think you might be feeling kind of...
嫉妒
jealous.
哦
Right.
好吧
Well, uh--
我不会嫉妒
l'm not jealous.
我只是想知道你介不介意
l just want to know if you're okay with all of this?
你介意吗
Are you?
我没事
l'm fine.
你好  我是尼克
Yeah, this is Nick.
- 请给我来杯啤酒  - 我一样
- Beer, please. - l'll have the same. Thanks.
像我这样的男人  很难找到真爱
Love in this world that is a hard thing for a man like me to find.
我觉得我们都在努力寻找真爱
Well, l think we all struggle with that particular little deal.
我考虑了下你说的建议
So l thought about what you said.
一开始的时候  我觉得你说得对
And at first l thought you were right.
我女儿需要很多机会
Opportunities are what my little girl should have.
然后  我仔细想了想  我爱我的女儿
Then, you know, l started thinking, l love my girl.
她也爱我
And she loves me.
这份爱值得她给我一次机会
And that love deserves an opportunity, as well.
所以我决定
So what l decided to do
在这个城市建立自己的家庭
is establish myself here in town and l'm gonna do my best to see
我会尽自己最大的努力  看看自己能不能成功
if l can set up some kinda life here.
我有点不太明白
l'm, uh-- not real sure what-- what you're saying.
法林先生  请不要把这个当成一次竞争
Mr. Fallin, don't think of this as a competition, please.
这不是竞争
lt's not that.
嗨  尼克
Hey, Nick.
- 嗨  - 嗨
- Hey. - Hey.
希望你不要介意我过来了
l hope you don't mind l'm up here.
不  这
No, it's--
我找到工作了
Got a job.
亨利汉堡屋
Henry's Burger House.
太好了
Great.
下周开始上班  最低工资加小费
Start next week. Minimum wage plus tips.
恭喜你
Congratulations.
我想来
l just wanted to, you know,
谢谢你
thank you.
你可以等明天再来
Yeah, well, you could've waited till tomorrow.
我在想  既然我现在找到了工作
l was thinking, now that l got this job
学校的事情也很顺利
and the whole school thing's working out--
是
Right.
我在想  我是不是可以
l was thinking maybe l'd, uh--
告诉辛迪事情的真相
l tell Cindy the truth about who l am.
你觉得我应该说吗
D'you think l should do that?
可以吧  随便你
Yeah, l guess. Whatever.
那我就去做了
Okay. Then l'm gonna do that.
祝我好运吗
Wish me luck?
祝你好运
Good luck.
你也走这边吗
You going out this way?
我也走这边
l'll come.
- 嗨  亲爱的  - 嗨
- Hey, honey. - Hey.
要喝点东西吗
Want something to drink?
亲爱的  关于收养的事
Sweetheart, about the adoption.
怎么了
Yeah?
你爸爸改变主意了
Your father changed his mind.
他不同意了
He's, uh-- he's not willing to give his consent.
什么意思
What's that mean?
那么  你
Well, you'll--
你还是会住在这里
you'd still be living here.
你说过你会收养我的
You said you were going to adopt me.
我知道  我也想  亲爱的
l know. l want to, honey.
你说过的
You said it.
我都已经告诉我的朋友了
l already told my friends.
香农
Shannon--
告诉我爸  他再也不是我爸了
Tell my dad that he's not my dad anymore.
你去跟他说
You tell him that.
没那么容易的  好吗
lt's not that simple, okay?
需要法庭的认可的  但是我
That would have to play itself out in court and l, uh--
但是  那很棒啊  你是个很了不起的律师  你可以赢的
But, that's good 'cause you're, like, this great lawyer, so you could win.
嗯
Yeah.
你可以赢的  伯顿
You can win, Burton.
我打给辛迪了  告诉她真相了
l called Cindy. Told her the truth.
我带她出去吃晚饭
Took her out to dinner.
就想你认为的那样  我应该告诉她
And like you seemed to think l should do, l told her.
关于没有去卡内基·梅隆念书
Yeah. About not really going to CMU.
关于我对计算机一无所知
The fact that, in reality, l know crap about computers in general.
- 好吧  - 她就把我甩了
- Okay. - And she dumped me.
你会找到新的女朋友的
You'll find another girl.
我不想要其他女孩  我想要辛迪
l don't want to meet another girl. l want Cindy.
她现在很恨我  所以  谢谢你
Now she hates me, so thank you.
如果我给她买个非常贵的戒指会怎么样
What if l bought a really expensive ring or something?
- 得了吧  朗尼- 不 你听我说
- Oh, Lonnie. - No, no, no.
如果我送她一个以前别人都没有送过她的东西
lf l bought her something that no one had ever gotten her before
她就会觉得我可以养她
so she'd think l was somebody who could provide for her.
不要那么做
Don't... don't do that.
哎  等会儿  企鹅在上映  我们可以一起去看
Hey, maybe later, the Penguins are on... We could hang out.
我要去下洗手间
Hey, you know what? l... l got... l gotta go to the bathroom.
那明天晚上吧  怎么样
What about... what about tomorrow night?
不行  我要工作
No, l gotta work.
是吗  那下周呢
Oh, yeah? What about next week?
抱歉  抱歉
Well, l'm sorry. Sorry.
嗨  他们准备进来了
Hey, they're ready to come in.
这些我经历过
l've been in this situation before.
是吗
Right.
很多次了
Many times before.
嗯
Okay.
我觉得我们最好都不要拐弯抹角了
l think it's best not to go through the whole charade.
结果总是一样的
lt always plays out the same way.
所以就跳过那些貌似有希望的部分  回到事实本身吧
So let's just skip the hopeful part of it and get on with the way that it is.
- 回到什么事实  - 生活
- Get on with what? - You know, life.
生活  生活怎么了
Life? Life being what?
你在公园吸毒  然后向陌生人卖淫的生活吗
You smoking crack in the park and having sex with strange men for money?
是啊  一次又一次
Yeah... in one iteration. Yes.
一次又一次
ln one iteration?
你和你父亲的问题  你还不能放手吗
These problems with your dad, are they worth dying over?
这太伤人了
That's melodramatic.
像你这种人活不久的
People like you don't survive very long.
- 像我  - 对  像你这种人
- Like me? - Yeah, like you!
这是我的选择
This is my choice!
那你为什么以开始还是回到了匹兹堡呢
Why did you come back to Pittsburgh in the first place, huh?
如果你这么恨你父母  你为什么还要回来呢
lf you hate your parents so much, why are you here?
我只是想让他们帮我照顾我的孩子们
l just want them to take care of my kids.
发生什么了  啊
What happened, huh?
你之前还说你想跟你父母一起住的
You said you wanted to live with your parents!
没有  那是你说的
No, you did!
所以  帮我告诉他们好吗
So you... Just tell them, okay?
告诉他们  谢谢他们
Tell them thank you very much.
法林先生  我们抓到一个
Mr. Fallin, we detained a young man
想要从你的支票账户提取5000美元的男子
who attempted to withdraw five thousand dollars from your checking account.
他掌握了你的所有信息
He had all of your information.
我们本来要报警了
Now, we were going to call the police,
但是他说你认识他  而且他这么做是经过你允许的
but he insisted that you knew he was here and had given your permission.
我们要不要报警
Would you like us to call the police?
嘿  嘿  你知道我以后肯定会还你钱的
Hey. Hey, you know l would... l would've paid you back.
我只是想给辛迪买那个戒指
l... l just... l wanted to get that ring for Cindy, you know?
法林先生  我很感激你没有报警
l really appreciate you not taking this badly, Mr. Fallin.
我非常感谢你
l mean, uh... l really appreciate it.
你明白吗  如果领养一旦生效
Do you understand that if this adoption decree is granted,
亨利就像所有的亲生婴儿一样
Henry will be the same as a natural child?
我明白
Yes.
你将有义务去教育  帮助
That you will have the duty to educate, support,
教导和培养他
and provide moral guidance and upbringing?
我明白
Yes.
你将有责任去关怀爱护他
That you have a duty of love and affection to show to this child?
我明白
Yes.
他可以继承你的财产  你也可以接受他的财产
That he may inherit from you and you from him?
我明白
Yes.
在他和未来你可能拥有的
That there can be no discrimination between this child
孩子之间不会有歧视
and any natural or adopted child you may have now or in the future?
我明白
Yes.
在明白了上述责任之后  你们希望收养亨利吗
Understanding these responsibilities, do you wish to adopt Henry?
我们希望
Yes.
法官大人  我同意此收养令生效
Your Honor, l move the adoption degree be... be entered.
搞定了
So ordered.
恭喜
Congratulations.
谢谢你  法林先生
Thank you, Mr. Fallin.
我昨晚给辛迪打电话了
So l tried to call Cindy last night.
她还是不想跟我讲话
She still won't talk to me.
好吧  我要忘记她了
Yeah, so... l'm over her, man.
我觉得你说得对  你猜怎么着
Hey, and you're right. You know that?
社区大学里会有很多靓妞的
There are lots of hot girls at community college.
不会那么自大
Not so, uh, stuck up.
看起来不错  对吧
That looks good, huh?
富兰克林  有个地方漏刷了
Franklin, you missed a spot.
喂  我朋友叫尼克·法林
Hey, my friend's name is Nick Fallin.
不叫富兰克林  是法林
Not Franklin. Fallin.
哦  但是还是漏了一块
Well, he missed a spot.
你知道吗  你没有漏刷
You know... you didn't miss a spot.
你知道的  对不对
You know that, right?
嗨  莎迪赛德人
Hey, Shadyside.
嗨
Hey.
天气变冷了
lt's getting cold.
Xgun擦枪小组 有偿招募译制成员 诚邀阁下
加入Q群：545053435
请注明职务：翻译、听译、aegisub特效（熟练手）
对字幕有任何意见和建议的同学请加Q群：544487177